https://www.bpsweb.org/privacy-statement/

Skip to content
MENUMENUHOMEABOUT BPS
Vision and Mission StatementHistoryWhat We DoAnnual ReportsAccreditation
BPS Appointed MembersBPS StaffEmployer Advisory Council RosterInternational Engagement CommitteeBPS Weaver/Penna Award
Specialty Councils
Ambulatory Care PharmacyCardiology PharmacyCompounded Sterile Preparations PharmacyCritical Care PharmacyGeriatric PharmacyInfectious Diseases PharmacyNuclear PharmacyNutrition Support PharmacyOncology PharmacyPediatric PharmacyPharmacotherapyPsychiatric PharmacySolid Organ Transplantation Pharmacy
IMPACT OF CERTIFICATION
BPS Board Certification in the Real WorldMaking a DifferencePeer Developed and RecognizedRewards of Certification
BPS SPECIALTIES
Ambulatory Care PharmacyCardiology PharmacyCompounded Sterile Preparations PharmacyCritical Care PharmacyGeriatric Pharmacy
Infectious Diseases PharmacyNuclear PharmacyNutrition Support PharmacyOncology PharmacyPediatric Pharmacy
Pharmacotherapy
Added Qualifications
Psychiatric PharmacySolid Organ Transplantation Pharmacy
SPECIALTY EXAM INFORMATION
RegisterCandidate’s GuideEmployer VerificationUpcoming Deadlines, Dates and Fees
Preparing for the ExamContent OutlinesExam Day: What to ExpectScoring Process
Exam Results HistoryFrequently Asked QuestionsTesting SitesWithdrawals and No Shows
Recertification
Overview of RecertificationAnnual Certification FeeApply for RecertificationDual and Multiple Specialty Recertification Offerings
Recertification GuideRecertification by Continuing EducationRecertification by Examination
MY BPS
REGISTERLOG IN
Resources
Education Documentation Request Form (International Applicants Only)Find A Board Certified PharmacistHelpful Tips for International CandidatesPetitioner's Guide for Recognition of a Pharmacy Practice SpecialtyRequest for BPS to Consider a New Specialty
BPS AmbassadorsBPS Digital BadgesBPS PoliciesBPS Seed GrantBPS Store
External LinksSample Questions
Media
BPS Fact SheetSpecialty Fact SheetsSpecialty BrochuresLeadership Blog
Press ReleasesPodcastsGeneral BPS VideosSpecialty Videos
Contact
Privacy Statement
BPS recognizes that users may have concerns about privacy issues as they navigate the Internet. BPS is committed to providing users with a safe, secure environment in which to secure information. We recommend visiting the Federal Trade Commission website for more information about general privacy issues.
BPS will use reasonable efforts to ensure that the information you provide remains private, and is used only for the purposes stated below.
Collected Information
We collect information about the users of our site. This information helps us determine which parts of the site visitors find most valuable as well as how we can continually improve the services we provide. User identities remain anonymous unless the User provides this information as a part of registration.
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our website.
Users may use our website without logging in, but logging in must occur in order to use any of the personalization services. Our site’s registration form requires specific contact information: name, e-mail address, etc., or to conduct e-commerce (e.g., pay annual fees, make purchases from our online store). The contact information is used to contact users when necessary.
Unique identifiers (such as IDs and passwords) are collected to verify the visitor’s identity and for use as account numbers in our record system.
Sharing of Certificant Data
If necessary for BPS’s ordinary course of business, and subject to appropriate contractual confidentiality protections, BPS may share certain personal information about applicants and certificants with third parties who use such personal information to provide core services to BPS or to assist BPS and individuals with the maintenance of those individuals’ certifications.
Review of Anonymous Data
We are committed to ensuring that our website contains content that is valuable and useful to our customers and potential customers who visit. To assist us in this, from time to time, we may implement the Google analytics demographics and interest reporting features on our website. These tools allow us to review anonymous data regarding the gender, age and interests of website visitors and adapt our website content to better reflect their needs. Although this information is collected through your Google ad settings, it is not provided to us in a personally-identifiable format. This means we cannot identify what information is about you, and we will not try to figure it out. If we do utilize this feature, you can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Google Ad settings or through the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on.
BPS may also use Google and Adobe analytics data and the DoubleClick cookie to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website.  Site visitors may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page or they may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics opt-out page or the Adobe Analytics opt-out page. Google has additional information available about their Remarketing Privacy Guidelines, Policies, and Restrictions.
Links to Other Sites
BPS may contain links to third-party websites. These links are provided solely as a convenience to users and not as an endorsement by BPS of the contents on such third-party websites. BPS is not responsible for the content of linked third-party sites and does not make any representations regarding the content or accuracy of materials on such third-party websites. Links to third-party websites are performed at your own risk.
BPS does not represent or guarantee the truthfulness, accuracy, or reliability of communications posted by users or endorse any opinions expressed by users. User acknowledges that any reliance on material posted by other users will be at the User’s risk.
E-mail messages
BPS communicates with its users by e-mail for specific Web-related functions, such password reminders. Because these messages are critical to site use, users will not be able to opt-out of receiving such messages.
Users who register with BPS have the option of receiving occasional e-mails from us about new features and similar messages that we feel may be of interest. Users may opt-in to receive these messages. The following options are available to opt-out of receiving these messages if Users have previously opted-in:
Edit User’s registration profile
Send e-mail to webmaster@bpsweb.org
Call 202-872-4499
Cookies
At BPS, we use a feature on your Internet browser called a “cookie”. A cookie is a small text file (often including a unique identifier) that is sent to a user’s web browser from a website’s computer and stored on a user’s computer’s hard drive or on a tablet or mobile device (collectively, “Computer”). A cookie stores a small amount of data on your computer about your visit to the website. Cookies do not collect any personal data stored on your hard drive or computer. BPS does not use cookies to collect any personal information about users, nor do we sell or make them available to other organizations.
Performance cookies collect information on how users interact with our websites, including what pages are visited most, as well as other analytical data. We use these details to improve how our websites function and to understand how users interact with them.
Under normal circumstances, cookies cannot transfer viruses or malware to your computer. Because the data in a cookie doesn’t change when it travels back and forth, it has no way to affect how your computer runs.
You may disable the cookie function on your browser or erase the contents in your cookies file. To do this, consult the help features on your browser. However, please bear in mind that doing this prevents the website from recognizing you as a previous user of this website and may prevent you from using some features on the site. You must have cookies enabled to create a BPS account.
Security
Your account containing your information is password protected and should never be shared with anyone. This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Please visit our page on security for more detailed information
Feedback
BPS encourages visitors to submit feedback. Any feedback that is submitted becomes the property of BPS and we may use this feedback for marketing purposes, or to contact visitors for more information.
Privacy Policy Updates
Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted here so that visitors will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about BPS’s privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, contact us at:
Board of Pharmacy Specialties
2215 Constitution Avenue, NW
Washington, DC 20037-2985
Phone: 202-429-7591
2215 Constitution Avenue, NW Washington, DC 20037-2985
|
Phone 202-429-7591
|
FAX 202-429-6304
|
© 2020 Board of Pharmacy Specialties
Go to Top
We are using cookies to give you the best experience on our website.
To learn more about our cookie and privacy policy, click here.
Accept
Close GDPR Cookie Settings
Privacy Overview
Cookie Policy
Powered by  GDPR Cookie Compliance
Privacy Overview
BPS recognizes that users may have concerns about privacy issues as they navigate the Internet. BPS is committed to providing users with a safe, secure environment in which to secure information. We recommend visiting the Federal Trade Commission website for more information about general privacy issues.
For more information about our Privacy Policy, click here.
Cookie Policy
At BPS, we use a feature on your Internet browser called a "cookie". A cookie is a small text file (often including a unique identifier) that is sent to a user's web browser from a website's computer and stored on a user's computer's hard drive or on a tablet or mobile device (collectively, "Computer"). A cookie stores a small amount of data on your computer about your visit to the website. Cookies do not collect any personal data stored on your hard drive or computer. BPS does not use cookies to collect any personal information about users, nor do we sell or make them available to other organizations.
You may disable the cookie function on your browser or erase the contents in your cookies file. To do this, consult the help features on your browser. However, please bear in mind that doing this prevents the website from recognizing you as a previous user of this website and may prevent you from using some features on the site. You must have cookies enabled to create a BPS account.
For more information about our Cookie Policy, click here.
Enable All
Save Changes
